it's tough you know the trading life
we're going to call it that it's tough
and I'm not talking about the skill
itself which is obviously difficult I
mean everything that goes with it and I
wanted to talk about that a bit you
probably noticed over the years that I
don't post as many videos and a big part
of the the reason for that is that the
trading industry has changed and I'm not
sure I completely relate to how things
are now it's all a bit fake and there's
nothing real about a lot of the advice
that's being given people giving advice
not really caring about whether the
advice is the right advice but just how
it makes them look and so I wanted to
have a bit of a real conversation as you
can imagine those of you that have been
watching the channel for a while you'll
know when I have these sorts of
conversations they'll be a bit rambly
there are a few things I want to speak
about and I think it'll be helpful for
some of you um but if you're not up for
a rambly video then obviously there's
plenty of other videos to watch
but we used to do these sort of I used
to call them onetoone videos many many
years ago and I stopped doing them
and the the thing with those videos what
ended up happening is that I'd get lots
of messages from young men who felt they
had connected with me in some way and
they'd send me messages and some of
these messages were really heavy you
know people going through really
difficult times struggling because of
trading because of other things and it
was heavy and it felt like a
responsibility because I'm the sort of
person who wants to solve everyone's
problems so when someone tells me
something that's going on then I'm
thinking about how I can actually help
them and what advice I can give but you
know and I'll I'll say this now and is
for this video as well as any other
advice I give that when it comes to the
mental side uh of trading or of life
I've read a lot of things and looked
into studies and research and all kinds
of things I know a lot about Psychology
and Neuroscience but I'm not a trained
professional I'm not a therapist or a
counselor or a psychologist or anything
like that uh I'm just a a guy who's been
through a lot in life achieved some good
things made a lot of bad mistakes and I
can only give you my advice things that
I've learned life advice but um the
reason I'm doing this video is because
on Friday I got a DM on Instagram and it
was a guy a young guy um saying that he
was feeling suicidal and I guess from
what he described and I obviously don't
know the whole and outs of it but
related to trading feeling like he's
behind in life that he's got no friends
he's dedicated his life to trading and I
guess he was feeling alone and those
that that sort of message is what I used
to get back in the day and I think over
time our videos have got less personal
I'm not really it's not really not
intentionally although maybe
subconsciously I'm not really connecting
with you guys as in I'm not giving you
anything to connect with it's more just
lessons like presenting the information
and and talking through things and not
really giving you the Human Side so it's
been a while since I had a message like
that and it kind of hit me because I
realized there are so many young men out
there that are struggling and sorry I
know that some of our audience are
female but when I look at the stats it's
over 90% male so I'm mainly talking to
the men here um although it would maybe
apply to you as well even if you're a
woman there's a lot of men and who are
feeling alone who are feeling desperate
and feeling like things are not going
well and that there's no light at the
end of the tunnel like things are pretty
bleak for them and it's particularly
true for people in the trading industry
because I think when it comes down to it
and this is what I've learned from now
years of experience of talking to people
that learning to trade and stuff most
people come into
trading not because of the money or
because of passion for the markets or
something like that well maybe because
of the money but not not so much because
of the passion for the markets which I
believe you need the passion for the
markets to truly succeed over the long
term but they're not coming into it for
that what they're coming into it for is
to fill a gap that they have in their
life to solve something that they
think's missing to be somewhere that
they feel like they can't get to
otherwise whether it be money status
having a purpose feeling like they're
important feeding like they can finally
do something that makes them stand
out having something that makes them
feel like they can work towards
something and then also like the the
benefits that come from money women
material items and things like that and
the thing is that trading can be a
lonely journey and it's it's tough and
there are going to be dark times and
when you first get started you've got
all the dopamine it's exciting when you
open trades it feels like uh thrilling
but there are going to be dark times and
it's especially true when you've gained
something and lost it like for example
if you get funded and then you lose the
funded account if you um have been
making profit for a month and then you
lose it all on one trade and suddenly it
all hits you and I don't think it's just
the sort of the downer from Trading that
hits you although that would be the case
like I don't want to get too sciency
here but you know there' be a rise in
cortisol you'll have less testosterone
at that time you're not getting the
dopamine from the good feeling of excuse
me closing
trades but alongside that um what you
have is that this Band-Aid that you've
put on whatever problem you have has now
been ripped off so if you were not
satisfied in life if you had some sort
of Gap that you were filling with
trading and that was giving you the hope
if suddenly that hope is gone like that
because you've lost money because you
aren't making a progress you want it's
like taking off the Band-Aids and it's
revealing the Gap that was there and
that's a difficult place to be in and
the truth is that life is tough life is
really tough you know back when I did
those videos years ago where I was
giving advice and like how to talk to
your family about trading about my
experience when I first make started
making hundreds of thousands of pounds
from trading it was good advice but I
was also relatively young and I've
experienced a lot since then and I can
tell you life is tough and it doesn't
matter if you succeed at trading or you
don't succeed at trading a lot of the
problems that you are experiencing now
you will still experience then like in
the future once you've succeeded so I'll
tell you a little bit about me and I
don't really like talking about myself
too much it might surprise you I talk a
lot but usually when the topic comes on
to me I change topics a lot of the time
so um I didn't have the best childhood I
had a really rough childhood and I'm not
really ready to talk about that publicly
I don't really talk about that but it
was tough and I grew up in a poor area
of London and going to school was tough
uh the environment I was in it just it
wasn't a nice
situation and so all I did was for a
while focused on my school until I got
involved ing gangs and stuff like that
which may surprise you to hear that from
me but I focused on school for a while
and I I was I always did quite well then
I went to University and I graduated and
I got a dream job I was working in
wealth management and I was working in
the sports and entertainment department
so I know there's an article that's
written about me online which claims
that I'm not telling the truth about it
for absolutely no reason at all but I
worked in sports and entertainment at a
very prestigious Bank uh Sports
entertainment mean those of the clients
that I had so when you pick up the phone
to talk to a client or you meet the
client it's often someone you know like
a household name or their accountant or
manager or something that you're dealing
with it's interesting job like dream
job and that was all I ever wanted at
that point was I wanted money I wanted
status I wanted women I was a bit of a
womanized let's be honest and all I ever
did was go out
drinking uh and doing things that would
like pay over the cracks for me and I
thought that making money would make
things better and it didn't and then I
like I've been I started learning about
the markets in about 2002 by 2012 I'd
made enough money that I could leave my
job in the bank and I've spoken about
this before um in the video that was
really popular at the time and saw like
400,000 views or something crazy like
that and the money I made just left me
Shell Shocked like I've made hundreds of
thousands of pounds in a really short
space of time I quit my job and I was
moving into a place in Zurich that was a
penthouse and life was good except as I
spoke about in that video I went through
one of the darkest times of my life and
I couldn't understand why and my
girlfriend left me and I was suicidal at
the time and yet I could afford to buy
whatever I wanted within
reason and everything I'd worked towards
was for that and
suddenly the problems were more
Amplified F than ever and I couldn't
figure it out and when I looked back to
it I realized that the problems were
always there and making money was or
like the this sort of destination I was
trying to reach was what made me not pay
attention to the problems that I had and
made me feel
like as long as I had that hope I could
just focus on that and things will be
better when I've achieved X or Y or Zed
and then when I achieved X and Y and Zed
then all I was left with were the
problems and the the funny thing in the
comments section on that video people
say this is first W problems I'd love to
swap your problems with mine and blah
blah blah but um well you never know
what problems someone's been through and
I'd been through a lot of a lot of [__]
and it completely broke me and I had a
breakup and that broke me and I had to
rebuild from what felt like nothing and
I had to figure out what I needed to do
to to fix my life I didn't intend to
talk about all this by the way this
feels like I'm in a therapy session or
something but I had a few points I
wanted to talk about and I thought the
best thing is to speak from the heart
and to give something real and now we're
drifting off into talking about my
background so um where am I going with
this I'm I'm trying to say
that a lot of the problems you're facing
now that you think trading is going to
solve need to be solved in a different
way and if you don't don't do that the
hard times you go through a trading are
going to hit you hard and even when you
succeed you'll get hit hard potentially
and I see like in our community there
are some people who you can just tell
they've had a stable childhood they
haven't had any difficulty in their
backgrounds they've probably never had
to struggle very well sort of
well-rounded stable people and are doing
it because they love the markets and I
mean some of the nicest people you ever
meet so don't get me wrong I'm not
knocking them but I just feel like they
it won't hit them so hard when they go
through tough times or they're probably
more likely to succeed at trading and
just be stable with it but I think if
you're watching this video you probably
are not in that category and
you like a lot of people that come in
trading have gaps in your life that
you're trying to F with this and hoping
this will be the
thing
um so it's it's tough tough like life's
tough and it it doesn't stop just when
you succeed at trading when you start
making lots of money when you're in
demand for your services and you can you
know in a blink from eye like pick up
the phone and and get a well-paid uh
Consulting gig or whatever it might be
it doesn't solve some of these core
problems it's not going to change your
life in the way that you think it will
it could make things worse I don't want
to sound all like I feel like I'm being
all like Doom and Gloom now but um but
the there's light at the end of the
tunnel anyway but the thing is the
problems don't stop what happens is that
you you get better at dealing with them
life itself teaches you how to deal with
life and I think these days it's very
easy for people to try and avoid
problems like people are hooked on
dopamine and there there are so many
ways to escape reality uh whether it's
social media computer games endless
music porn whatever it might be there
are so many ways to escape reality that
when things get tough it's easier for
people to escape but you have to go
through the tough times to learn how to
get through more tough times and it does
get easier I remember when I was at
University I was going through a really
difficult time and I was in a pub with
my girlfriend at the time ex now and
um a few other people and one of the
guys he was a bit older he was like in
his 30s or something and all of us we
were in our were like 19 20 or something
like that one of the guys I knew also he
was after my girlfriends but fortunately
it was too old for her overweight and um
face looked like hit by a spade so uh
there was no
competition but he gave me advice that
didn't mean anything to me at the time
but I've thought about a lot over the
years recent years he said as you get
older it becomes much easier to live
with yourself and to bring this all back
to the point of what I'm trying to say
here is that when you're young and
you're going through these problems and
it feels like the world's crashing
around you give it 10 years and you'll
look back at it and two things one it
won't seem so bad and two you'll be
grateful for the experience because
you'll notice other problems that came
up later that made it it was much easier
to deal with because of what you'd gone
through at an earlier age so don't get
to the point where you think this is it
this is the end of everything because of
these things I'm experiencing like I've
lost my friends I've lost this I've lost
that I've not achieved this I'm feeling
like I'm behind in life because all of
my friends have now got promotions in
their job and I committed myself to
trading it's not the end of the world
like it feels like it is at that time
things do get easier like when I talked
about in that video uh that my
girlfriend broke up with me and I went
into meltdown and I loved her and it
felt like I'd lost my entire future but
then what happens is you move on you
meet someone better and I did and I was
with that person for eight years and
actually just last week we broke up and
we were about to start a family together
so it's painful um but it's so much
easier to deal with now because I've
dealt with that in the past and so
things get easier but you have to tackle
things head on um don't feel like you
need everything right now and don't feel
like everything that you want right now
will always be the most important thing
to you when you're young and you're
seeing people on social media I think
it's so difficult growing up these days
like I grew up with some social media
like Myspace and stuff like that and
then Facebook when we were at University
but and so on I think now it's so
difficult cuz you're constantly
comparing yourself to people and when
you're comp comparing yourself to people
it's it can be hell I often say that
even someone that lives in a remote
Village and it's just them and one other
person even they will not be happy
comparing them to comparing themselves
to someone even if they don't have
social media if they're next door
neighbor the only person that's in their
area they live in is doing better than
them they'll still feel it the only way
you escape it is to be completely on
your own away from anyone so you can't
compare yourself to anyone at all or to
accept yourself and say I just need to
focus on myself and what I've got anyway
I'm going off on a tangent but um when
you're young you feel like all the
things you want are the most important
things and if you want uh Lamborghini
and penth houses and things like that
it's like when you're not getting it it
feels miserable and it feels like if
you're not going to achieve that what's
the point of living But as time goes on
the things that you find important
change and you might look back on those
things and think I never needed them in
the first place and actually your
priorities change and the things that
you want in life change the things that
you're willing to do for different
things changes it's like when I was
younger all I cared about was what
people thought of me so I was there on
social media and this is long before Doo
and long before Instagram Traders
existed I was there on my Facebook
posting going on a yacht holiday car
moving into a pen I was spending lots of
money for for not for me but just for
what people thought of me I cared about
how I look uh I cared about how I came
across to
people and as you get older sorry if you
can hear the sirens going past they
coming to arrest me cuz I'm speaking too
openly um as you get older these things
don't matter so much like I don't care
how people see me I don't even have a
car anymore I was spending at one point
6 and a half Grand a month for a
penthouse I just live in like a a humble
apartment now like things change like
priorities changed I don't care about
how I look in fact my as you can
probably see my hair is falling out and
it doesn't really matter that much I was
going to get a haircut the other day and
my usual Barber he has moved back to
Romania so I've got this new guy and I
went there one time and he didn't say a
word to me he was silent so I went there
the second time expecting him not to say
anything to me but he does so he's like
ask me what I want obviously and then he
gets the Clippers out to get started and
he opens his mouth to say something to
me I'm like he talks really quietly I'm
listen to him and he says don't you want
a hair
transplant and I was like thanks mate
good confidence boost there I fancy that
being the only thing you ever say
someone don't you want a hair transplant
but these things don't matter and
um you can't pin all of your whole world
on everything on something you're trying
to
achieve and then feel like it's the end
of the world when you don't get it when
give it a few more years time you maybe
wouldn't even want it wouldn't be as
important to you and especially if you
start feeling suicidal about it to feel
like you want to end your life or
there's nothing worth living for for
over something that you temporarily want
it's just not worth it and the truth is
once you've achieved the things that you
think you
want let's say that you make lots of
money and you can go and get table
service in clubs and you can fly first
class or even a private jet and live in
pen houses and drive a
Supercar when you have all that stuff
sometimes it feels empty because the
thing that you wanted is something that
you lost along the way and that's
something that you can make sure right
now now that you don't lose along the
way so I've lost friends I've lost
relationships I've sacrificed my
well-being and if I could go back and
give myself some advice it would be to
have more balance trading is not the be
or and end or if trading is what you
want to do doesn't mean it's has to be
the only thing you do and I encourage
everyone to prioritize if trading is
meant to be your priority to make sure
that you're taking the actions that make
it a priority that shouldn't come at the
expense of other things like okay the
basics like sleeping well eating well
exercising every day is important for
knowing is it going to improve your
well-being but it's also going to
improve your trading performance but
then
also not losing contact with
friends spending time with your
family letting people know that you care
about them stuff that I didn't do you
know a lot of people want to hear my
trading advice about like this is what
you should do with your risk management
this is how you you should analyze the
markets this is what you do with your
system and then when it comes to all the
other stuff they're like you know
closing off and don't want to hear it
but I think the best advice I can give
to anyone is to learn from my mistakes
and I've made many of them along the way
that I've been very lonely at times
because I didn't look after the
relationships that I had I mean look
just finished like uh it's not directly
to do with with trading and stuff but
I'm sure that me working all hours son
or the sun didn't help and it's same
with previous
relationships and I should learn from my
mistakes but I don't always but you can
learn from my mistakes I'm sure you'll
make some for
yourself you shouldn't abandon your
family there's nothing Noble in
sacrificing absolutely everything
there's these days of like you know
people like Andrew Tate or things like
that and they say a lot of good stuff
but they also make it seem like all you
need is to be in good shape have lots of
money and everything else fine
but but that's not everything and and
you'll feel it later in life if if
that's what you're focused on let me
just quickly check my notes see what I'm
missing here so before we go any further
there are three things that I want to
ask of you the first thing is that let
me know if you want more videos like
this or not I know it's a bit rambly and
start stop because I'm just literally
talking from the heart here not scripted
anything I've only got some some brief
notes you can literally see there it's
just on the pad let me know if you want
ones like this or if you just think like
shut up and get one with the trading
lessons then fine um that's the first
thing the second thing is that there's a
community here whether you realize it or
not and I'm not talking about the dyo
community that's one thing and it's the
best community in the world for trading
I mean here in the comments section here
on YouTube there's a community and you
can help each other because in those
times when you're thinking that you're
on your own you'll quickly realize that
you're not on your own but you need to
reach out to people people so the first
thing was about whether you want these
videos the second thing is that if you
are going through a tough time right now
if you're experiencing difficulty you
feel alone things aren't going how you
thought they would leave a comment and
let people know your your situation
create a burner account if you need to
so it's not on your name or something
but let people know in the comments what
you're going through and the third thing
is for those of you who are a bit older
like me and you've been through some
[__] to go in the comments and let those
people know what they need to
know either in reply to them or leave a
post saying what you went through how
you overcame it how your perspective on
life has
changed just that
simple Insight that simple bit of
experience can mean the world to someone
else so if you would take a moment to
share that that would be
amazing
um I think like with all of this uh with
trading I think the thing that you need
to think think about is what are you
really doing this for and don't just say
it's for the money or because you're
interested in the markets there's
something deeper why do you want money
is it to fix your problems in that case
you know getting a job can sometimes be
easier there are easy ways to make money
is there something deeper going on like
the thing I realized uh
that that drove me for a long time and
to this day I mean this the whole
[__] reason that I'm doing D in the
first place really is
some sort of validation to make me feel
like the things that I was working on
had a purpose not just making money for
myself but
like I don't know well I do know but I'm
not wanting to talk about it so I do
know exactly what I want to say but so
what is it for you and is it something
that could be achieved easier without
having to sacrifice things because maybe
it can if it's about status is there a
different way to get that if it's about
being appreciated is there a different
way to get that I could tell you for
sure people appreciate you a lot more
for the care you give them and the
attention you give them and the love you
give them than they will the money you
give them and how you financially
support them and you should do both if
you can but don't disregard that
especially relationships for those of
you that are male and you're in a
relationship with a
woman that I've found over the years and
have continuously made this mistake that
they don't necessarily want the fancy
things I can buy them they want my
attention and my time and to feel like I
care about them and not like they're
just a placeholder or someone that I
will spend time with only when I need a
break from work so these these things
matter a lot but figure out what it is
that you want because the thing is when
you get too lost
inside trading and working all the time
and reading self-help books and focusing
on the gym and all these different
things that are great
in
moderation is that it's really easy to
lose yourself and you need to figure out
what it is that you actually want
because at some point in your life you
are going to have to figure that
out and it can take some time there was
this guy that I met I was in molter on
holiday and he was a bartender and he
was coming over and bringing our drinks
and stuff and my girlfriend was in the
toilet X girlfriend now was in the
toilet that's going to be my my my uh
catchphrase from now on that's the story
of my life
um but that's that's a warning to you
about working too much so she was in the
toilet and he came over and he mentioned
something about
that about his ex-girlfriend he' just
broken up and he mentioned something
about it but the way he mentioned it it
was it was so obvious it was a cry for
help that this guy just needed someone
to talk to so I said hey like tell me
more about it and turns out he had no
friends he was like over from another
country just studying there didn't
really have any friends he could talk to
who couldn't talk to his parents and he
was just feeling alone so we exchanged
numbers and I spoke to him for like a
well all the time end up hiring him for
6 months cuz he needed a job at one
point and what I realized is that this
was a guy like me and like so many other
people who didn't really have a
relationship with their dad and
therefore was trying to figure things
out for themselves and felt they had no
direction in life and rather than
choosing something and going for it or
realizing what they wanted to needed
they're just jumping from one thing to
another one friend group to another one
job to another one hobby to another just
trying to figure something out because
they just felt
lost and that's a tough place to be in
I'm sure some of you watching if you've
made it this far we're like uh how far
are we into this video Now 26 minutes
geez I need to wrap this up soon going
on way too long
um some of you will be feeling that as
well and
the only thing I can say is that you you
have to be a bit
introspective when I was in my early 20s
there's no way that I would have thought
about talking to people these days it's
been two and a half years now that I've
been going to therapy once a week and
it's not like people say oh he talking
about your emotions it's not it's about
speaking out loud and someone paying
attention to all your of what you're
saying understanding the context of your
life because of hours of listening to
you talk about it and being able to give
you the right perspective back because
sometimes we're like this like we have
our problems and situations and we can
only see one solution which is to keep
doing what we're doing and hope that it
changes things and it's just someone
that helps you expand your thinking and
to to realize um how you can approach
things differently like for example a
guy I was speaking to on Friday who's
feeling
suicidal the things I was trying to
mention to him is just
to to think about other Solutions
there's a whole world out there so many
things that we can do there are so many
ways to overcome problems but when
you're in that problem you feel like you
have one solution or that you're just
going to keep going until that thing
gets better or like you just wonder what
you can do there are so many solutions
to things so I think being introspective
talking to people helps getting therapy
if you can afford it or if it's free
wherever you live um can help but really
it's talking to people either in the
comment section here in our community
that we have or friends and family
you know for men it's so difficult to
talk to people because you feel
like you feel like if you reveal your
problems you're weak and as much as I
feel like I can communicate things
Sirens again as much as I feel like I
can communicate things and I'm sharing
some personal things with you now I also
struggle with this like I spoke to my
friend the other day he was calling me
see was telling me that uh him and his
wife are having a baby this was my best
friend my closest friend we lived
together for years and talking to him I
didn't even know that he was on
medication for anxiety didn't know that
he didn't know that I had a family
member who tried to commit suicide last
year we were just like hold on a
second we were so close we don't know
anything about each other and we're like
okay we'll talk more and I know it's
like we won't talk more but there are
people that are there for you and there
are people that you can talk to and you
just have to nurture those relationships
and not feel like you're completely on
your own it does get easier over time
problems getas easier to deal with you
grow up you learn you know you toughen
up it's like what David Goggins talks
about like callousing your mind all
these problems you're going through are
not going to they're not going to do you
in they're not going to kill you I mean
obviously some problems can but the the
problems you're facing as a result of
trading in this lifestyle they're not
going to kill you they're actually going
to toughen you up and it's going to make
it much easier to deal with things
unless you avoid them and take the easy
route of escapism and stuff like that
all right the camera cut off there and I
don't know where I was where we got up
to then um
hopefully didn't cut off Midway through
an important point but anyway I think
that I've I've pretty much said most of
what I want to say it's mainly that
things are tough but they do get
better uh it gets easier over time as
long as you don't avoid things by you
know escapism and stuff and the solution
to everything is not just getting in
shape making money and attracting women
there's there's things deeper that we
need to resolve and it's tough being a
man it's tough being a young man and
especially if you don't have a father
figure or you've got gaps in your life
that you think you need to fill with
something but things get easier and
you're not on your own there are people
around you you can talk to whether in
the comment section here whether friends
like I said family who would be there
for you nurture those relationships or
if you're going to do it on your own
then fine but just just know that you
know I I can't help everyone but I
understand and I'm Testament to the fact
that you go through a lot of [__] in
life and get through the other side and
be a better person for IT be more
successful but also more someone that
people can depend on and that you feel
that you could depend on yourself and
you can get through anything it's
possible to get to that place now one
thing that I'm not sure if I'm going to
keep in or not but up here by my desk I
have uh framed a poem and it's if by
rogard kitlin and I feels a bit cringe
to read this out but I'm going to do it
anyway because I think this means a lot
and sometimes I read this and I feel
like a little it like I can feel it in
me like it's a bit emotional to read it
and it's you to read it and really
internalize it and think about it when I
read this I think this is the sort of
stuff I should have got from from a dad
uh it says if you can keep your head
when all about you are losing theirs and
blaming on you if you can trust yourself
when all men doubt you but make
allowance for their doubting too if you
can wait and not be tired by waiting or
being lied about don't deal in lies or
being hated don't give way to hating and
yet don't look too good nor talk too
wise if you can dream and not make
dreams your master if you can think and
not make thoughts your aim if you can
meet with Triumph and disaster and treat
those two imposters just the same if you
can bear to hear the truth You' spoken
Twisted by naves to make a trap for
fools or watch the things you gave your
life to broken and stoop and build them
up with worn out tools if you can make
one heap of your winnings and risk it on
one turn of pitch and toss and lose and
start again at your beginnings and never
breathe a word about your loss if you
can force your heart and nerve and Sen
to serve your turn long after they're
gone and so hold on when there's nothing
in you except the will which says to
them hold on my hairs are standing on
end if you can talk with crowds and keep
your virtue or walk with Kings nor lose
the common touch if neither foes nor
loving friends can hurt you if all men
count with you but none too much if you
can feel the unforgiving minute with 60
seconds worth of distance run yours is
the Earth and everything that's in it
and which is more you'll be a man my son
so my hairs are standing on in now that
it just means a lot to me that poem
because going through tough times man is
tough it's tough and you get through the
other side and you never want to go
through it again but you know you're
better off for it so if you made it this
far thanks for listening to me rambling
I'm sorry maybe at times it was a little
bit self- serving and stuff but I found
it quite theraputic and maybe it helped
you so if it did leave a comment down
below let me know if you want more of
these sorts of videos it won't be as
long in future I promise you um leave a
comment letting me know letting everyone
know about your situation if you're
going through difficulty you need to
speak to someone so you're not alone
even if you do it on a burner account
and for those of you that have been
through some [__] let everyone know
about what you've been through how you
got through the other side give people
that bit of Hope and support the others
who maybe need someone on their side at
a moment thanks for watching I'll see
you next time